Guide to the Savage Mining Company and Associated Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 10.25; (13 boxes)
  - ORE AND BULLION RECORDS
    - Savage Mining Company
      - Bullion shipped to San Francisco, 1868-69 (Box 86, Folder 1421)
  - Unidentified Ore Records
    - Ore assay reports, 1871 (Box 86, Folder 1422)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS
    - Hale & Norcross Mining Company
      - President in account with superintendent, 1888, 1890 (Box 87, Folder 1423)
    - Lady Bryan Mining Company
      - Receipts, 1877 (Box 87, Folder 1424)
    - Savage Mining Company
      - General Records
        - Receipts, 1862-90 (Box 87, Folder 1425)
      - Bank Records
        - Bank of California, Virginia City: check stubs, 1869 (Box 87, Folder 1426)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Accounts, 1868, 1877 (Box 87, Folder 1427-28)
    - Unidentified Financial Records
      - Bank records: checkbook cover, 1873 (Box 87, Folder 1429)
    - Savage Mining Company
      - Bank Records
        - Bank of California, Virginia City: check stubs, 1893-96 (Box 88a, Folder 1429a)
        - Paxton & Thornburgh: check stubs, 1863-64 (Box 88, Folder 1429b-33)
  - INVENTORY RECORDS
    - Savage Mining Company
      - Savage Assay Office
        - Store and stock expense summary, 1871-75 (Box 89, Folder 1434-38)
  - PAY ROLL RECORDS
    - Lady Bryan
      - Pay roll records, 1876-77 (Box 89, Folder 1439)
    - Santiago Mill
      - Pay roll records, 1882, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 1440)
    - Savage Mill
      - Pay roll record, 1871 Jun (Box 89, Folder 1441)
    - Savage Mining Company
      - Ledgers
        - Pay roll records, 1883 (Box 89, Folder 1442)
        - Pay roll records, 1886-87 (Box 89, Folder 1443)
        - Pay roll records, 1892-93, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 1444)
      - Daybooks
        - Time book, 1873 Jan-Feb (Box 89, Folder 1445)
  - TAX RECORDS
    - East Sierra Mining Company
      - State and county tax statements, 1895-96 (Box 90, Folder 1446)
    - Hale & Norcross Mining Company
      - State and county tax statements, 1883-85,1887 (Box 90, Folder 1447)
    - Justice Mining Company
      - State and county tax statements, 1894-95 (Box 90, Folder 1448)
    - Savage Mining Company
      - State and county tax statements, 1866-1903 (Box 90, Folder 1449-51)
      - Poll tax records, 1865 (Box 90, Folder 1452)
    - Scorpion Mining Company
      - State and county tax statements, 1895-96 (Box 90, Folder 1453)
    - South Comstock Mining Company
      - State and county tax statements, 1894-96 (Box 90, Folder 1454)
    - Unidentified Tax Records
      - Notes, 1882-83 (Box 90, Folder 1455)
  - MINING COMPANY FORMS
    - Executive Records (Series I)
      - In account with T. H. Ralston, Commission Stock Broker, ca. 187- (Box 91, Folder 1456)
    - Ore and Bullion Records (Series II)
      - Hale & Norcross Silver Mining Co. Statement of Bullion Produced, ca. 187- (Box 91, Folder 1457)
      - Memorandum of Bullion from Hale & Norcross Mine, Assayed at Hale & Norcross Assay Office, ca. 187- (Box 91, Folder 1458)
      - Statement for the Comstock Tunnel Co., ca. 189- (Box 91, Folder 1459)
      - Ore_____Mill,_____1872. [assay report], ca. 1872 (Box 91, Folder 1460)
      - Statement of Taxable Property within Storey County, Nevada, ca. 188-, 190- (Box 91, Folder 1461)
  - TAILINGS
    - Storey County Tax List for 1889. Printed by Wm. Sutherland, Virginia City, Nevada., 1889 Sep 2 (Box 91, Folder 1462)
  - OPERATION RECORDS
    - Savage Mining Company
      - Savage Mine
        - Weekly reports of ore production and expenses, 1865 (Box 92, Folder 1463)
        - Weekly reports of ore production and expenses, 1869 (Box 92, Folder 1464-65)
        - Weekly reports of ore production and expenses, 1869-70 (Box 93, Folder 1466-69)
    - Unidentified Operation Reports
      - Reports of operations, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1470)
      - Maps of the mine levels, 1887, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 1471)
  - INVENTORY RECORDS
    - Atchison Mill
      - Store house accounts, 1869 (Box 94, Folder 1472)
    - Savage Mill
      - Store house accounts, 1869-70 (Box 94, Folder 1473)
  - MINING COMPANY FORMS
    - Inventory Reports (Series V)
      - Savage Mining Company. Store House report, ca. 1872 (Box 94, Folder 1474)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 9; (18 boxes)
  Restricted Fragile Papers, contains fragile originals. The material is arranged in folder order.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 5-7 (Box 95, Folder 1475)
  - Box 1, folder 8-9 (Box 95, Folder 1476-78)
  - Box 1, folder 13 (Box 95, Folder 1479)
  - Box 1, folder 14 (Box 95, Folder 1480-81)
  - Box 1, folder 15 (Box 95, Folder 1482)
  - Box 3, folder 35-36 (Box 95, Folder 1483)
  - Box 3, folder 40-42 (Box 95, Folder 1484)
  - Box 4, folder 46-49 (Box 95, Folder 1485)
  - Box 4, folder 50 (Box 95, Folder 1486)
  - Box 4, folder 51 (Box 95, Folder 1487)
  - Box 4, folder 52 (Box 95, Folder 1488)
  - Box 5, folder 55-56 (Box 95, Folder 1489)
  - Box 5, folder 57 (Box 95, Folder 1490)
  - Box 5, folder 58 (Box 95, Folder 1491)
  - Box 5, folder 63-68 (Box 95, Folder 1492)
  - Box 5, folder 69-70 (Box 95, Folder 1493)
  - Box 5, folder 71 (Box 95, Folder 1494)
  - Box 6, folder 73-75 (Box 95, Folder 1495)
  - Box 6, folder 76 (Box 95, Folder 1496)
  - Box 6, folder 80 (Box 95, Folder 1497)
  - Box 6, folder 81-82 (Box 95, Folder 1498)
  - Box 6, folder 86 (Box 95, Folder 1499)
  - Box 7, folder 101 (Box 95, Folder 1500)
  - Box 10, folder 190 (Box 95, Folder 1501)
  - Box 12, folder 233-35 (Box 96, Folder 1502)
  - Box 12, folder 236-37 (Box 96, Folder 1503)
  - Box 13, folder 254 (Box 96, Folder 1504)
  - Box 13, folder 262 (Box 96, Folder 1505)
  - Box 13, folder 264-70 (Box 96, Folder 1506-07)
  - Box 14, folder 274-81 (Box 96, Folder 1508-11)
  - Box 15, folder 282-90 (Box 96, Folder 1512)
  - Box 15-16, folder 291-99 (Box 96, Folder 1513)
  - Box 16-17, folder 300-11 (Box 96, Folder 1514)
  - Box 17, folder 318-19 (Box 96, Folder 1515)
  - Box 17, folder 321 (Box 96, Folder 1516-17)
  - Box 17, folder 324 (Box 96, Folder 1518)
  - Box 24a, folder 358a-f (Box 96, Folder 1519)
  - Box 25, folder 362 (Box 96, Folder 1520)
  - Box 25, folder 363 (Box 96, Folder 1521)
  - Box 25, folder 366-84 (Box 96, Folder 1522-24)
  - Box 26-27, folder 400-21 (Box 96, Folder 1525-26)
  - Box 27, folder 428-33 (Box 96, Folder 1527-30)
  - Box 27, folder 440-47 (Box 97, Folder 1531-37)
  - Box 27, folder 453-55a (Box 97, Folder 1538-44)
  - Box 28, folder 456-59 (Box 98, Folder 1545-51)
  - Box 28, folder 462-73 (Box 98, Folder 1552-54)
  - Box 28, folder 483-87 (Box 98, Folder 1555)
  - Box 29, folder 488-90 (Box 98, Folder 1556-57)
  - Box 29, folder 491-92 (Box 98, Folder 1558)
  - Box 29, folder 502-11 (Box 99, Folder 1559-61)
  - Box 29-31, folder 512-32 (Box 99, Folder 1562-64)
  - Box 31-32, folder 533-41 (Box 99, Folder 1565)
  - Box 32-34, folder 542-62 (Box 99, Folder 1566-68)
  - Box 34-37, folder 563-84 (Box 99, Folder 1569-76)
  - Box 37-39, folder 585-98 (Box 100, Folder 1577-82)
  - Box 39-40, folder 599-611 (Box 100, Folder 1583-85)
  - Box 40, folder 612-24 (Box 100, Folder 1586-90)
  - Box 41, folder 639 (Box 100, Folder 1591)
  - Box 41, folder 640 (Box 100, Folder 1592)
  - Box 41, folder 647 (Box 100, Folder 1593)
  - Box 44, folder 730 (Box 100, Folder 1594)
  - Box 45, folder 762-64 (Box 100, Folder 1595)
  - Box 45, folder 765-67 (Box 100, Folder 1596)
  - Box 45, folder 768-71 (Box 100, Folder 1597-99)
  - Box 45-46, folder 772-82 (Box 100, Folder 1600)
  - Box 46, folder 786-87 (Box 100, Folder 1601)
  - Box 46, folder 788-89 (Box 100, Folder 1602-06)
  - Box 46, folder 790-94 (Box 101, Folder 1607-08)
  - Box 46, folder 795 (Box 101, Folder 1609)
  - Box 46, folder 796 (Box 101, Folder 1610)
  - Box 46, folder 797 (Box 101, Folder 1611)
  - Box 47, folder 798-99 (Box 101, Folder 1612)
  - Box 47, folder 800-02 (Box 101, Folder 1613)
  - Box 47, folder 803-06 (Box 101, Folder 1614-15)
  - Box 47, folder 807-09 (Box 101, Folder 1616-20)
  - Box 47, folder 810-13 (Box 101, Folder 1621-26)
  - Box 48, folder 814-16 (Box 101, Folder 1627)
  - Box 49, folder 829-37 (Box 101, Folder 1628)
  - Box 50, folder 843-51 (Box 101, Folder 1629)
  - Box 50-51, folder 852-64 (Box 101, Folder 1630)
  - Box 51-52, folder 865-69 (Box 101, Folder 1631)
  - Box 54, folder 882-89 (Box 101, Folder 1632)
  - Box 55, folder 897-99 (Box 101, Folder 1633)
  - Box 55, folder 903-09 (Box 101, Folder 1634)
  - Box 56, folder 922-23 (Box 101, Folder 1635)
  - Box 57, folder 944-46 (Box 101, Folder 1636)
  - Box 62, folder 1046 (Box 101, Folder 1637)
  - Box 63, folder 1077-79 (Box 102, Folder 1638-39)
  - Box 63, folder 1080-89 (Box 102, Folder 1640-42)
  - Box 64-65, folder 1100-08 (Box 102, Folder 1643-49)
  - Box 75, folder 1253-62 (Box 102, Folder 1650)
  - Box 75-76, folder 1263-71 (Box 102, Folder 1651)
  - Box 76, folder 1279-84 (Box 102, Folder 1652-53)
  - Box 76, folder 1285-91 (Box 102, Folder 1654)
  - Box 77, folder 1309-14 (Box 102, Folder 1655)
  - Box 78, folder 1315-20 (Box 102, Folder 1656)
  - Box 78, folder 1327-31 (Box 102, Folder 1657-61)
  - Box 78, folder 1332-35 (Box 103, Folder 1662-64)
  - Box 79, folder 1336-41 (Box 103, Folder 1665)
  - Box 79, folder 1343 (Box 103, Folder 1666)
  - Box 28, folder 461 (Box 104, Folder 1667)
  - Box 89, folder 1434-38 (Box 104, Folder 1668)
  - Box 90, folder 1449-51 (Box 104, Folder 1669)
  - Box 8, folder 133-36 (Box 105, Folder 1670)
    This material has been filmed and reproduced in the collection in copyflow. The film's call number is MS Vault / Microfilm / 674
  - Box 8, folder 137-39 (Box 105, Folder 1671)
  - Box 9, folder 141-46 (Box 106, Folder 1672)
  - Box 9, folder 147-50 (Box 107, Folder 1673)
  - Box 9, folder 151-52 (Box 107, Folder 1674)
  - Box 9, folder 153-54 (Box 107, Folder 1675)
  - Box 70, folder 1183-94 (Box 108, Folder 1676)
  - Box 88, folder 1432 (Box 109, Folder 1677)
  - Box 89, folder 1445 (Box 109, Folder 1678)
  - Box 59, folder 973-74 (Box 110, Folder 1679)
  - Box 59, folder 982-83 (Box 111, Folder 1680)
  - Box 60, folder 984-85 (Box 112, Folder 1681)
  - Box 61, folder 1017 (Box 113, Folder 1682)